Art of Latin America since Independence Photograph Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 277. Piza, Arthur Luiz (Brazil, 1928- ) (Box 4)
  - Untitled, 1959 (Box 4)
- 278. Plaza, Ezequiel (Chile) (Box 4)
  - The Bohemian Painter (Box 4)
- 279-280. Poleo, Hector (Venezuela, 1918- ) (Box 4)
  - Persistence of Memory, 1963-1964 (Box 4)
  - The Three Commissioners, 1942 (Box 4)
- 281. Polesello, Rogelio (Argentina, 1939- ) (Box 5)
  - Indigenous Images, 1962 (Box 5)
- 282. Ponce, Bernal (Chile, contemporary) (Box 5)
  - The Flight (Box 5)
- 283. Ponce de Leon, Fidelio (Cuba, 1895-1949) (Box 5)
  - Two Women, 1934 (Box 5)
- 284. Portinari, Candido (Brazil, 1903-1961) (Box 5)
  - Coffee, 1935 (Box 5)
- 285. Porto Alegre, Manuel de Araujo (Brazil, 1806-1879) (Box 5)
  - Caricature of Justiniano Jose de Rocha (Box 5)
- 286. Portocarrero, Rene (cuba, 1912- ) (Box 5)
  - Cathedral, 1961 (Missing, 2007) (Box 5)
- 287. Posada, Jose Guadalupe (Mexico, 1851-1913) (Box 5)
  - Female Dandy (Missing, 2007) (Box 5)
- 288. Potyguara, Lazzarotto, Called Poty (Brazil, 1924- ) (Box 5)
  - The Brakeman, ca. 1944 (Box 5)
- 289. Pradier, Charles Simon (Switzerland, 1783-1847) (Box 5)
  - Dom Joao VI, ca. 1818-1820 (Box 5)
- 290. Pucciarelli, Mario A. (Argentina, 1928- ) (Box 5)
  - Composition, 1963 (Box 5)
- 291-293. Pueyrredon, Prilidiano (Argentina, 1823-1870) (Box 5)
  - A Rest in the Country, 1861 (Box 5)
  - A Sunday in the Suburbs of San Isidro (Box 5)
  - Sra. Eastman de Barros, 1865 (Box 5)
- 294. Quinquella Martin, Benito (Argentina, 1890- ) (Box 5)
  - New Bridge (Box 5)
- 295. Quiroa, Marco Augusto (Guatemala, 1937- ) (Box 5)
  - The Tastacan, 1963 (Box 5)
- 296. Ramirez Rosales, Manuel (Chile, 1804-1877) (Box 5)
  - Landscape with Palm Trees (Box 5)
- 297-298. Ramirez Villamizar, Eduardo (Colombia, 1923- ) (Box 5)
  - Black and White No. 1, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Model for relief mural, Bank of the Republic, Cucuta (Box 5)
- 299. Ramos Martinez, Alfredo (Mexico, 1875-1946) (Box 5)
  - Old Bretons (Box 5)
- 300. Renart, Emilio J. (Argentina, 1925- ) (Box 5)
  - Untitled, 1965 (Box 5)
- 301. Rendon, Manuel (France, 1894- ) (Box 5)
  - Untitled (Box 5)
- 302. Reschreiter, Rudolf (Germany, 19th century) (Box 5)
  - Sangay, 1904 (Box 5)
- 303-304. Reveron, Armando (Venezuela, 1889-1954) (Box 5)
  - The Cave, 1920 (Box 5)
  - Landscape, 1929 (Box 5)
- 305-312. Rivera, Diego (Mexico, 1886-1957) (Box 5)
  - Building the Palace of Cortes, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Design for the Anahuacalli, ca. 1950 (Box 5)
  - Day of the Dead in the Country, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Flower Vendor, 1935 (Box 5)
  - Man at the Crossroads, 1932 (Box 5)
  - The New Freedom, from "Portrait of America" serie, 1933 (Missing, 2007) (Box 5)
  - Portrait of a Man, 1913 (Box 5)
  - Sleep, 1932 (Box 5)
- 313. Roa, Israel (Chile, 1909- ) (Box 5)
  - Cemetery of Saint Ines (Box 5)
- 314. Rodriguez Padilla, Rafael (Guatemala, 1890-1929) (Box 5)
  - Still Life, 1927 (Box 5)
- 315. Rodriguez Roda, Juan Antonio, called Roda (Colombian, b. Spain, 1921- ) (Box 5)
  - Philip IV, 1965 (Box 5)
- 316. Rojas, Cristobal (Venezuela, 1858-1890) (Box 5)
  - Study of the Balcony (Box 5)
- 317-320. Rugendas, Johann Moritz (Bavaria, 1802-1858) (Box 5)
  - Portrait of the Princess of Joinville, 1846 (Box 5)
  - Plaza de Armas (Box 5)
  - Return of Garibaldi after the Battle of San Antonio (Box 5)
  - Valparaiso Fire (Box 5)
- 321. Ruiz, Antonio (Mexico, 1897- ) (Box 5)
  - The New Rich, 1941 (Box 5)
- 322. Sabatier, after Lauvergne, Berthelemy (latter b. France, 1805-1871) (Box 5)
  - Vue de port de Guayaquil (Box 5)
- 323. Sabogal, Jose (Peru, 1888-1956) (Box 5)
  - The Dealer in Antiques, 1949 (Box 5)
- 324. Sabogal, Jose (Peru, 1888-1956) (Box 5)
  - Mulatto Tamale Vendor, 1926 (Box 5)
- 325. Saez, Carlos Federico (Uruguay, 1878-1900) (Box 5)
  - Portrait of a Young Lady (Box 5)
- 326. St. Aulaire, Felix Achille, after Sarokins, S. (latter British?, 19th century) (Box 5)
  - View of Veracruz (Box 5)
- 327. Salas, Rafael (Ecuador, 1830-1906) (Box 5)
  - Quito (Box 5)
- 328. Sanchez Elia, F. Peralta Ramos, A. Agostini and C. Testa (Argentina, contemporary) (Box 5)
  - Bank of London and South America, Buenos Aires, 1960 (Box 5)
- 329-330. Santa Maria, Andres de (Colombia, 1860-1945) (Box 5)
  - Portrait of Lady (Box 5)
  - Still Life (Box 5)
- 331. Santos Chavez, Jose (Chile, 1934- ) (Box 5)
  - Southern Images, Cover I (Box 5)
- 332. Serpa, Ivan (Brazil, 1923- ) (Box 5)
  - 15th of March, 1952 (Box 5)
- 333. Sheridan, Enrique (Argentina, 1838-1863) (Box 5)
  - A Street in San Isidro (Box 5)
- 334. Simone, Alfredo de (Italy, 1898-1950) (Box 5)
  - The Street (Box 5)
- 335. Sinclair Ballesteros, Alfredo (Panama, 1916- ) (Box 5)
  - Marañon - from the series "City without Lights", 1963 (Box 5)
- 336-337. Sivori, Eduardo (Argentina, 1847-1918) (Box 5)
  - Landscape "The Bather" (Box 5)
  - Portrait of the Artist's Wife (Box 5)
- 338. Soto, Jesus (Venezuela, 1923- ) (Box 5)
  - Vibration, 1964 (Box 5)
- 339. Souza, Gerson Alves de (Brazil, 1926- ) (Box 5)
  - Purgatory, 1965 (Box 5)
- 340-341. Spilimbergo, Lino Eneas (Argentina, 1896-1964) (Box 5)
  - Still Life (Box 5)
  - Figures (Box 5)
- 342-343. Squirri, Carlos (Argentina, 1934- ) (Box 5)
  - Cancer, 1957 (Box 5)
  - Sectioned Hand, 1964 (Box 5)
- 344. Subercaseaux, Ramon (Chile, 1854-1936) (Box 5)
  - The Mouth of the River at Viña del Mar (Box 5)
- 345. Szyszlo, Fernando de (Peru, 1925- ) (Box 5)
  - Cajamarca, 1963 (Box 5)
- 346. Tabara, Ernesto (Ecuador) (Box 5)
  - View of Guayaquil from the Airplane, 1964 (Box 5)
- 347-349. Tamayo, Rufino (Mexico, 1889- ) (Box 5)
  - The Fountain, 1951 (Box 5)
  - Homage to the Race, 1952 (Box 5)
  - The Flute Player (Missing, 2007) (Box 5)
- 350-351. Tatis, Jose Gabriel (Colombia, 1813-?) (Box 5)
  - Self-Portrait, 1853 (Box 5)
  - Prominent Gentlemen of Bogota, 1853 (Box 5)
- 352-353. Taunay, Nicolas Antoine (France, 1755-1830) (Box 5)
  - Carioca Square in 1816 (Box 5)
  - Jeanneton (Box 5)
- 354. Testa, Clorindo (Argentina, b. Naples, 1923- ) (Box 5)
  - Painting, 1961 (Box 5)
- 355. Tolsa, Manuel (Spain, 1757-1816) (Box 5)
  - Plan for the School of Mines, Mexico City, 1819 (?) (Box 5)
- 356. Toral, Mario (Chile, 1934- ) (Box 6)
  - Untitled (Box 6)
- 357. Torres, Mariano de Jesus (Morelia, Mexico, 19th century) (Box 6)
  - Closed Street of San Agustin, Morelia, 1874 (Box 6)
- 358-360. Torres Garcia, Joaquin (Uruguay, 1874-1949) (Box 6)
  - Abstract Composition, 1937 (Box 6)
  - Constructive Ship "America" (Missing, 2007) (Box 6)
  - Portrait of Velazquez, 1945 (Box 6)
- 361. Torres Mendez, Ramon (Colombia, 1809-1885) (Box 6)
  - Country Types (Box 6)
- 362-363. Tovar y Tovar, Martin (Venezuela, 1828-1902) (Box 6)
  - Juan Verrue, 1877 (Box 6)
  - Self-Portrait, 1855 (Box 6)
- 364. Troya, Rafael (Ecuador, 1845-1921) (Box 6)
  - The Shore, 1905 (Box 6)
- 365. Trujillo, Guillermo (Panama, 1927- ) (Box 6)
  - Mother Fury, 1964 (Box 6)
- 366. Turner, Charles (England, 1773-1857), after Gil de Castro (Peru ? -1841?) (Box 6)
  - Simon Bolivar, 1830 (Box 6)
- 367. Ugarte Elespuru, Juan Manuel (Peru, 1911- ) (Box 6)
  - Cartoon for Mural Painting in the Mercedes Cabello School, Lima, 1945 (Box 6)
- 368-369. Urteaga, Mario (Peru, 1875-1957) (Box 6)
  - The Bethrothed, 1937 (Box 6)
  - Burial of Illustratious Man, 1936 (Box 6)
- 370. Valencia, Cesat (Ecuador, 1918- ) (Box 6)
  - Caricature of Jose Gabriel Navarro, 1942 (Box 6)
- 371. Valenti, Carlos (Guatemala, 1891-1912) (Box 6)
  - Jaime Sabartes, 1911 (Box 6)
- 372. Vasarely, Victor (Hungary, 1908- ) (Box 6)
  - Mural for the Central University of Venezuela, 1952 (Box 6)
- 373. Vega, Jorge Luis de la (Argentina, 1930- ) (Box 6)
  - Music Hall, 1963 (Box 6)
- 374. Velasco, Jose Maria (Mexico, 1840-1912) (Box 6)
  - The Valley of Mexico Seen from the Hill of Guadalupe, 1905 (Box 6)
- 375-376. Victoria, Miguel Carlos (Argentina, 1884-1955) (Box 6)
  - Nude (Box 6)
  - Nude, 1923 (Box 6)
- 377-378. Vidal, Emeric Essex (England, 1791-1861) (Box 6)
  - Country Race (Box 6)
  - Estancia Foreman of the Epoch of Astigas (Box 6)
- 379. Vilches, Eduardo (Chile, 1932- ) (Box 6)
  - The Perez, 1964 (Box 6)
- 380. Villacis, Anibal (Ecuador, 1927- ) (Box 6)
  - Untitled (Box 6)
- 381. Villanueva, Carlos Raul (England, 1900- ) (Box 6)
  - 4 Preliminary Sketches for University City, Central University of Venezuela, Caracas, ca. 1946 (Box 6)
- 382-383. Vinatea Reynoso, Jorge (Peru, 1900-1931) (Box 6)
  - San Martin, 1921? (Box 6)
  - Straw Boats of Lake Titicaca, 1930 (Box 6)
- 384. Visconti, Elyseu D'Angelo (Italy, 1867-1944) (Box 6)
  - Sra. Nicolina Pinto Do Cuoto (Box 6)
- 385. Viteri, Oswaldo (Ecuador, 1931- ) (Box 6)
  - Still Life Painting in Maroon and Ochre, 1960 (Box 6)
- 386-389. Williams, Amancio (argentina, 1913- ) (Box 6)
  - Concert Hall; Project. Acoustical Studies, 1941; project, 1942-45/1953 (Box 6)
  - Concert Hall; Project. Acoustical Studies, 1941; project, 1942-45/1953 (Box 6)
  - Suspended Office Building; Project, 1946 (Box 6)
  - House in Mar del Plata, 1943-1945 (Box 6)
- 390-391. Wulf, Lloyd (U.S.A., active Ecuador, 1940-1965) (Box 6)
  - Two Men and Wine (Box 6)
  - Evocation of Trees (Box 6)
- 392. Yrarrazaval, Ricardo (Chile, 1942- ) (Box 6)
  - Standing Figure (Box 6)
- 393.Zachrisson, Julio (Panama, 1930- ) (Box 6)
  - Witch's Funeral, 1963 (Box 6)
- 394. Zalce, Alfredo (Mexico, 1908- ) (Box 6)
  - Parade of the Shoesshine Boys, 1941 (Box 6)
- 395. Zañartu, Enrique (Chilean, b. Paris, 1921- ) (Box 6)
  - Personages, 1956 (Box 6)